<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BostonTourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="category_eat">Eat</string>
    <string name="category_play">Play</string>
    <string name="category_stay">Stay</string>
    <string name="category_shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="category_tour">Tour</string>
    <string name="boston">Boston, MA</string>
    <string name="about_boston">About Boston</string>

    <!-- Info about Boston -->
    <string name="city">Boston is Massachusetts\' capital and largest city.Founded in 1630,
    it\'s one of the oldest cities in the U.S. The key role it played in the American Revolution
     is highlighted in the Freedom Trail, a 2.5 mile walking route of history sites that tells
    the story of the nation\'s founding.One stop, former meeting house is Faneuil Hall, is
    a popular marketplace."Beantown" is home to Symphony Hall, where the legendary Boston Pops
    orchestra performs, and Fenway Park, where the beloved Red Sox baseball team plays.
    Famous cultural institutions include the Museum of Fine Arts, Museum of Science, and the
    Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum, housing a world-class collection in a space designed like
    a 15th-century Venetian palazzo.</string>
    <string name="sky">Blue Sky</string>
    <string name="homes">Boston Homes on the charles and mystic rivers</string>
    <string name="weather_in_boston">Weather in Boston</string>
    <string name="seasons">SPRING\nAverage temperatures: 58°F to 72°F\nSpring is the Boston
        area\'s most spectacular time of the year. From early March into early June, enjoy the
        vibrant colors of azaleas, dogwoods and other flowers in bloom.\n\nSUMMER\nAverage
        temperatures: 78°F to 80°F\nThe Boston region\'s warm, sultry summers are punctuated
        by cooling coastal breezes and passing afternoon winds - all of which invite
        visitors to slow down, sip something refreshing and relax for a while.\n\nFall\nAverage
        temperatures: 58°F to 76°F\nFall in the Boston region brings with it days of bright
        sunshine, clear blue skies, golden marshes and perfectly crisp evenings.\n\nWINTER\nAverage
        temperatures: 10°F to 29°F\nTypically mild, winters in the Boston region are cold with
        periods of rain and the chance of snow flurries or heavy at times come late December or
        early January. January is the coldest.</string>
    <string name="image_of_item">Image of Item</string>
    <string name="dividing_bar">Dividing Bar</string>
    <string name="antico_forno"> Antico Forno </string>
    <string name="antico_forno_address">93 Salem Street\nBoston,MA</string>
    <string name="antico_forno_phone">(617) 723  &#8211;6733 </string>
    <string name="antico_forno_info">Located in Boston\'s North End, Antico Forno\'s specialty is
        Southern Italian cuisine,distinctly fresh and savory.In an atmosphere that is casual and
        relaxed, enjoy delicious food,with reasonable prices. The first glimpse of the wood-burning
        stove warms the soul and gives an immediate boost to the appetite. Full bar, private dining room,
        reservations recommended.</string>
    <string name="antico_forno_website">https://www.anticofornoboston.com/</string>
    <string name="legal_sea_foods">Legal Sea Foods</string>
    <string name="legal_sea_foods_address">1 Seafood Way\nBoston ,MA</string>
    <string name="legal_sea_foods_phone">(617) 530 &#8211;9000 </string>
    <string name="legal_sea_foods_info">The signature dish at Legal Sea Foods – really fresh fish.
       With over 40 varieties of fresh fish and shellfish available throughout the year as well
        as an award-winning wine list, there’s no doubt why legions of fans have fallen hook,
        line and sinker.#1 Best Seafood Restaurant” (USA Today, 2013), “Most Popular Boston Restaurant</string>
    <string name="legal_sea_foods_website">https://www.legalseafoods.com/</string>
    <string name="boston_chops">Boston Chops</string>
    <string name="Boston_chops_address">1375 Washington Street\nBoston,MA</string>
    <string name="boston_chops_phone">(617) 227 &#8211;5011 </string>
    <string name="boston_chops_info">An urban steak bistro, a casual, yet refined twist for which
        steakhouses are well-known.</string>
    <string name="boston_chops_website">http://www.bostonchops.com/</string>
    <string name="charles_river">Charles River</string>
    <string name="boston_common">Boston Common Park</string>
    <string name="neaquarium">New England Aquarium</string>
    <string name="charles_river_address">Storrow Drive,Boston,MA</string>
    <string name="boston_common_address">139 Tremont Street\nBoston,MA </string>
    <string name="neaquarium_address">1 Central Wharf,Boston,MA</string>
    <string name="charles_river_phone">(617)635 &#8211;4505</string>
    <string name="boston_common_phone">(617) 635 &#8211;4505</string>
    <string name="neaquarium_phone">(617) 973 &#8211;5200</string>
    <string name="charles_river_website">https://www.criver.com/</string>
    <string name="boston_common_website">https://www.boston.gov/parks/boston-common</string>
    <string name="neaquarium_website">http://www.neaq.org//</string>
    <string name="charles_river_info">
The Charles River flows 80 miles from Hopkinton, Mass. to Boston Harbor. The Charles River is the most
        prominent urban river in New England. It is a major source of recreation and a readily-available
        connection to the natural world for residents of the Boston metropolitan area. The entire
        Charles River drains rain and melted snow from a watershed area of 310 square miles.
        Two hundred and sixty-eight square miles of that watershed area drain over the Watertown Dam
        into the Lower Charles River. </string>
    <string name="boston_common_info">Boston Common is a central public park in downtown Boston, Massachusetts.
        It is sometimes erroneously referred to as the Boston Commons. Dating from 1634, it is the
        oldest city park in the United States.Families come to this treasured remnant of 17th century
        Boston for leisure – to stroll, jog, skate on the Frog Pond, and play in the ball fields. </string>
    <string name="neaquarium_info">The New England Aquarium is an aquarium located in Boston, Massachusetts.
        In addition to the main aquarium building, attractions at the New England Aquarium include
        the Simons IMAX Theatre and the New. The new England Aquarium is home to thousands of aquatic
        animals–from striped pyjama Sharks to giant Pacific octopus to little blue penguins.</string>
    <string name="faneuil_hall">Faneuil Hall Market Place</string>
    <string name="boston_farmers">Boston Farmers market</string>
    <string name="shops">Shops In Boston</string>
    <string name="faneuil_hall_address">4 S Market St,\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="boston_farmers_address">100 Hanover St,\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="shops_address">800 Boylston St,\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="faneuil_hall_phone">(617) 523 &#8211;1300</string>
    <string name="boston_farmers_phone"> (617) 973 &#8211;4909</string>
    <string name="shops_phone"> (617) 236 &#8211;3100</string>
    <string name="faneuil_hall_website">https://faneuilhallmarketplace.com/</string>
    <string name="boston_farmers_website">https://bostonpublicmarket.org/</string>
    <string name="shops_website">http://www.prudentialcenter.com/</string>
    <string name="faneuil_hall_info">Located in the heart of downtown Boston, Faneuil Hall Marketplace
        is adjacent to historic Faneuil Hall and is bordered by the financial district, the waterfront,
        the North End, Government Center and Haymarket. It is a well-traveled part of Boston’s “Freedom Trail.
        The Marketplace is a five-minute walk to the New England Aquarium, The Children’s Museum,
        The Old State House, and Paul Revere’s House.”</string>
    <string name="boston_farmers_info">The Boston Public Market is an indoor, year-round marketplace
        featuring 35 New England artisans and food producers housed under one roof offering fresh foods,
        prepared meals, crafts, and specialty items. Residents and visitors alike can find seasonal,
        locally sourced food from Massachusetts and New England, including fresh produce, meat and
        poultry, eggs, dairy, seafood, baked goods, specialty items, crafts, and prepared breakfast,
        lunch, and dinner options. Everything sold at the Market is produced or originates in New England.</string>
    <string name="shops_info">
For those of you who favor urban chic, the traditional and classic or upscale funky, our shops and
        stores are certain to please. The quality and versatility of our imaginative boutiques,
        eclectic galleries and prestigious department stores are only rivaled by our distinctive
        shopping districts where you can browse the glass-enclosed arcades at Copley Place, Prudential
        Center and CambridgeSide Galleria, meander the open-air Faneuil Hall Marketplace, Legacy Place
        and Patriot Place and seasonal artisan pop-ups and stroll the brownstone boutiques and shops
        along Newbury and Charles Streets. </string>
    <string name="omni_parker_house">Omni Parker House</string>
    <string name="marlowe">Kimpton Hotel Marlowe</string>
    <string name="ames">Ames Boston Hotel</string>
    <string name="omni_address">60 School St, Boston, MA</string>
    <string name="marlowe_address">25 Edwin H Land Blvd, Cambridge, MA </string>
    <string name="ames_address">1 Court St, Boston, MA</string>
    <string name="omni_phone">(617) 227 &#8211;8600</string>
    <string name="marlowe_phone"> (617) 868 &#8211;8000</string>
    <string name="ames_phone"> (617) 979 &#8211;8100</string>
    <string name="omni_website">https://www.omnihotels.com/hotels/boston-parker-house</string>
    <string name="marlowe_website">http://www.hotelmarlowe.com/</string>
    <string name="ames_website">www.amesbostonhotel.com</string>
    <string name="omni_info">A legendary symbol in downtown Boston since 1855, Omni Parker House
        boasts old-world charm and elegance accompanied by all of the modern conveniences of a
        world-class establishment. Nestled in the heart of our historic city, we’re located along the
        Freedom Trail and at the foot of Beacon Hill, Boston Common, Quincy Market and Faneuil Hall
        Marketplace. Logan International Airport is just 2.3 miles away.</string>
    <string name="marlowe_info">Our guests’ curiosities are piqued from the moment they enter our
        welcoming courtyard, which happens to showcase a 25-foot-tall sculpture named Celeste that
        moves and lights up. Based upon this awe-inspiring first impression, it quickly becomes clear
        that we encourage a sense of discovery and exploration that perfectly complements our storied
        Boston home. Visitors immediately learn to love our riverside Cambridge hotel’s decadent and
        engaging and intuitive style and level of service that elevates the experience time and again.</string>
    <string name="ames_info">Blending modern style in a historic building, Ames Boston Hotel, Curio
        Collection by Hilton provides a luxurious, boutique setting with a refined yet playful
        atmosphere. The Romanesque architectural styling combines with modern, sleek elements creating
        a unique vibe in the heart of downtown.</string>
    <string name="duck_tours">Duck Tours</string>
    <string name="harbor_cruises">Harbor Cruises</string>
    <string name="freedom_trail">The Freedom Trail</string>
    <string name="duck_tours_address">4 Copley Pl #4155,\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="harbour_cruises_address">62 Long Wharf,\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="freedom_trail_address">44 School St #250,\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="duck_tours_phone">(617) 267 &#8211;3825</string>
    <string name="harbor_cruises_phone"> (617) 227 &#8211;4321</string>
    <string name="freedom_trail_phone"> (617) 357 &#8211;8300</string>
    <string name="duck_tours_website">http://www.bostonducktours.com/</string>
    <string name="harbor_cruises_website">https://www.bostonharborcruises.com/</string>
    <string name="freedom_trail_website">http://www.thefreedomtrail.org</string>
    <string name="duck_tours_info">Boston Duck Tours is a great way to start off your visit to Boston.
        We give you a great overview of the city, show you many unique neighborhoods and splash you
        into the Charles River for a breathtaking view of the Boston and Cambridge skylines.</string>
    <string name="harbor_cruises_info">For more than 90 years, BHC and the Nolan family have been leading
        the way with outstanding cruises on Boston’s historic harbor. What began with a man, a boat
        and a vision has grown into today’s BHC; with 500 daily departures, 53 vessels and 250
        year-round employees, plus a seasonal workforce topping 650</string>
    <string name="freedom_trail_info">Welcome to the Freedom Trail, a 2.5-mile, red-lined route that
        leads you to 16 historically significant sites — each one an authentic treasure. Explore
        museums and meetinghouses, churches, and burying grounds. Learn about the brave people who
        shaped our nation. Discover the rich history of the American Revolution, as it began in
        Boston, where every step tells a story. </string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="weather">Weather</string>
</resources>

